moretvtime.com 2019-03-30

# More Tv Time

More Tv Time is committed to maintaining the safety your personal and non-personal data. We value the trust of our visitors and want to assure a safe browsing experience, according to the Data Protection Act, 1998. Any information we may collect from our users will not fall into misuse, and it will not be given or sold to any third party. Its purpose will only be used for the good functioning of our website, and in no way to infringe upon your security.

More Tv Time takes matters of user protection and privacy seriously. We are aware that you care about what we do with the personal information you have shared, so you can trust that we will treat it with care and never hinder your user experience.

This Privacy Policy’s aim is to reassure and inform our users about how we collect and use their personal data after they visit More Tv Time. If you have questions or feedback, don’t hesitate to contact us at any time.

What Personal Information We May Collect  
Every time a user visits our website, registers, contacts us, comments, or subscribes to our newsletter, they share personal data. This implies only their name and email address that More Tv Time will need in order to respond to their feedback, questions, or suggestions. Your personal information will not be given or sold to any third parties without your consent nor will it be used for commercial or advertising purposes.

Each time you visit our website, we may collect information indirectly regarding your browser type and Internet Protocol (IP) address, through cookies. “Cookies” are pieces of data that carry virtual information about you and are stored in your computer. It includes information about your browsing experience, such as the URL you came from to our site and the URL you went to after exiting. For More Tv Time, cookies help us gather information that we can use to improve your browsing experience. They are not used to identify you, such as your name or email address.

What We Will Do With Your Personal Data  
We will store all your shared personal information in a safe place, where no third party will have access. More Tv Time is fully aware that you wish to remain anonymous, so no user details will be shared, sold, or abused. However, we may use your shared information to:

Respond to your browsing needs better by personalizing your web surfing experience.  
Take note of your feedback in order to improve our website.  
Answer any questions or suggestions you may have.  
If you subscribe to our newsletter, we will send periodic emails about the latest content published on More Tv Time.  
Other Sites  
While browsing through our website, keep in mind that content on More Tv Time may include links to other sources. We cannot control their Privacy Policy terms, so we strongly advise you read them, as they may differ from our own and we cannot claim responsibility for their practices. This privacy policy applies only to More Tv Time. Other sites might insert other types of cookies, files on your computer, or request other personal information. If you have any security concerns, it’s encouraged that you read their privacy policy before going any further, as we cannot guarantee your web surfing safety after leaving our site.

Privacy Policy Changes  
More Tv Time reserves the right to make changes to our privacy policy. Every such modification will be added to this page with the date of its last revision. Should we feel the need to make consistent and major changes, we will add a notice on the website’s home page for both visitors and registered users. However, More Tv Time has no intentions on changing its policy in the near future because we firmly believe we excel at protecting our users’ privacy. Unless any laws change which will require adhering to, we may not feature an alternation in our policy in the foreseeable future.

Questions  
If you have any questions regarding More Tv Time’s Privacy Policy, we encourage you to contact us.

This Privacy Policy is governed More Tv Time’s Terms of Use Agreement, which we encourage you to read as well.
